carpartsdiscount.com 2007-02-03

# Privacy Policy

---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

**About this Privacy Policy:**  
    The entire site, or at least specific portions of this site are assisted by Zoovy technology. Zoovy has created this privacy policy as a template for customers who are using Zoovy technology with their websites. Zoovy in no way takes responsibility for the accuracy or enforcement of this policy. For a copy of Zoovy's privacy policy (which does not necessarily apply to the customers of its customers) visit http://www.zoovy.com/legal  
  
_Zoovy, Inc. has created this privacy statement for Car Parts Discount, Inc. in order to demonstrate our joint commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:_

Zoovy.com tracks IP Addresses

    Your IP address is used to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Web site, in addition your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart (in conjunction with a cookie.) We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.  
  
This site may contains links to other sites.   
    Car Parts Discount, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, unless otherwise specified below your information is never shared with other companies, even those who are also using Zoovy technology. In the future Zoovy may provide you the ability to share your information across multiple websites which all utilize Zoovy technology however this will only be done at your explicit request.  
  
This site requires Unique Identifiers.  
    This site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services, it also collects visitor's contact information (like their email address), in some circumstances their unique identifiers (like their pets name, or mothers maiden name), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future informational mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below, users may NOT opt out of receiving order notifications, or other contacts which are deemed essential by Car Parts Discount, Inc..  
  
This site requires Financial Information.  
    Financial information that is collected is used to bill the customer for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as pets name, and mothers maiden name) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.   
  
This site may have Surveys and/or Contests.  
    Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. This site may also run contests in which case we may ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). Generally this information is used to verify eligibility, however we may also use contact data from our contests to send users information about Car Parts Discount, Inc.. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary (for example winners). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected from our users is used to check the users' qualifications for registration and bill the user for products and services. 

This site may contain Public Forums

    This site may include chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

About our System Security

    This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Information is stored behind a firewall, against a password protected database system. Whenever sensitive information is accessed it is transmitted using strong SSL encryption. Car Parts Discount, Inc. may keep a copy of your information on its own system using Zoovy's WebAPI system, this system may have its own security measures in place. 

This site provides the choice to Opt In or Out

    Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Each time an information email is distributed, you have the option to use unique unsubscribe url which is attached to each outgoing email. Customers may unsubscribe at any time by simply logging into their accounts.  
  
We provide the ability to Correct/Update YOUR information.  
    This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Simply visit the customer login area of this website.  

Contacting the Web Site

    If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   
| By Mail: |  Car Parts Discount, Inc.  
P.O. Box 940881Simi ValleyCA93094  
  
---|---  
By Phone: |  (888) 437-4272  
  
or Email: |  [info@carpartsdiscount.com](mailto:info@carpartsdiscount.com)  
  
**Amendments made directly by Car Parts Discount, Inc.:  
**   
No amendments have been made.
